<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Numerology</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">open</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">cloase</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="HealthWellness">Health &amp; Work</string>
    <string name="dateofbirthselect">Please select your date of birth. Yur Life Path Attitude &amp; Birth Number will be Calculated based on Date of Birth</string>
    <string name="enternametext">Please enter your name</string>

    <!--rasifal-->
    <string name="Aries">
        All your hard work done in the past will be paid off during this year. You will get a hike in your salary with incentives. There are also bright possibilities for freshers to find a suitable job or start something of their own. Those of you who are single can get married. Some of you could be blessed with a child this year. This is a good period to attain high status in your job. Those working in the field of public life can achieve favourable results. A career change is likely in the month of May and July. Students will perform exceptionally well this year. There will be opportunities in your career to travel abroad. Some of you can get settled in a different country.
    </string>
    <string name="Taurus">
        Taurus: Some of you can pursue higher education or learn any new skill this year. Those in business will have lot of gains and profits. There will be growth in career and those unemployed will get a job. A new job responsibility can be given to you. Your professional bonding will improve and you will have better coordination with your subordinates and the other team members. This is a good time to invest in property. On the family side, health of your mother needs to be supervised. Your relationship with elder siblings will improve. Students will have a favourable time as their focus and attention in studies will improve
    </string>
    <string name="Gemini">
        Gemini: This year you will have new goals and desires and there will be positive changes in your professional life. You will have some sudden financial gains this year. Working professionals may get increments or opportunities to earn better after April. Entrepreneurs will be able to make better profits and expand their business which will enhance their source of earning. The year will bring luck and success in business and in any kind of partnership work. You will get help from influential people. Income from multiple sources is indicated. Those in a relationship are advised to introspect. Newly married couples will be blessed with a child.
    </string>
    <string name="Cancer">
        Cancer: This year will be favourable especially for those who are into real estate or property dealing business. They will crack some good deals. Those who are planning to buy a house or make renovations in their house will get support from near and dear ones. This year is also favourable if you are planning to have some rental business or let out your property for rental income. Health of family members need to be taken care. Professionally, you may feel lost, distracted and stressed as your plans will take time to materialise. Personally, you can face misunderstandings with your partner due to the intervention of family or friends in your relationship.
    </string>
    <string name="Leo">
        Leo: You will set high targets and will successfully achieve them. You will be able to resolve the problems you have been facing in the past. The month of March and April will be full of unexpected occurrences. The planetary position can give rise to some health problems, hence take good care. It can lead to a good professional relationship with your seniors and boss. This will directly impact your reputation at work and can increase the possibility of landing a promotion or increment. Between April and September, married couples will get over their marital woes and can plan to go on a trip with their spouse. Your bond with your extended family and friends will improve.
    </string>
    <string name="Virgo">
        Virgo: You will enjoy abundant wealth and financial prosperity during the beginning of 2022. There may be difficulties with which you may be able to deal with confidence. There will be positive energy around you. You will get plenty of motivation and inspiration to work harder. Corporate professionals can expect a promotion. Individuals who are planning to change their industry will be successful. People who are currently unemployed will get a job in 2022. Utilise your experience in the workplace to save yourself from getting into any unexpected situation. However, things can go downhill on the health front and you are prone to suffer from minor issues relating to stomach.
    </string>
    <string name="Libra">
        Libra: This year will inspire you to work harder. Changes and opportunities will be the norm this year. The time is also beneficial for freshers as they may get their dream job. This period will be good for students who are preparing for Law, Chartered accountancy and administrative jobs. Those who are employed may get good incentives and increments due to their capabilities. However, do not overexert yourself. Those who are planning to move out from their native place for studies will get good opportunities and will be able to enroll in the university of their choice. This year will also bring good gains from business. You can plan to construct your house or purchase a property.
    </string>
    <string name="Scorpio">Scorpio: You need to be cautious about your public image. Around April, the time is favourable for freshers searching for jobs as they will find some good proposals. The employed natives will also be able to dictate their terms at their workplace and will be in a commanding position. There are possibilities of increments and promotions. You may earn from more than one source or expansion of your business. Students can start earning from their hobbies. Your relationship with your children will improve and they will do some things which will make you feel proud. You should plan more of recreational activities. You may suffer from eye infections.
    </string>
    <string name="Sagittarius">
        Sagittarius: When it comes to money or finances, you need to be prudent else there can be financial problems. You are advised not to invest money in any speculative business as you may land up into losses. You will perform better in your business and will be recognised. In the second half of the year, your domestic life will be harmonious. Students can face distractions in studies due to peer pressure. They can also face concentration issues. The time will be favourable for those who are in a romantic relationship. The intensity of love and passion in the relationship will increase. Also, singles have bright chances of getting committed in a romantic relationship.
    </string>
    <string name="Capricorn">
    Capricorn: This year you may make new friends and expand your network by making influential contacts. There will be peace and happiness in the family, and an atmosphere of joy will prevail for most of the year. This time period will be beneficial for businessmen, especially those who are into family business. You will make some good profits and gains from your work. Also, there may be some sudden gain from stuck up resources. Your speech will be a bit harsh therefore be careful while talking to anyone as your rude words may hurt your near and dear ones. Healthwise, issues of self and family members may be the reason for your mental stress during this year.
</string>
    <string name="Aquarius">
        Aquarius: Your savings will improve during this year. You will get support from your immediate family in all your endeavours. You will plan frequent celebrations with your friends and family to mark your success. Those who plan to expand their business will get success. Government employees will have bright chances of a transfer. There are also possibilities of a change in job for those who have been looking for one. The time is favourable for short journeys as they will bring productive results. You will have to be careful while talking to your siblings and friends as your harsh words and aggressive gesture may bring differences in your relationship.
    </string>
    <string name="Pisces">
        Pisces: This year will be empowering for your personal self; you will feel more confident and stronger. You will have a charm on your face and wisdom in your words. You can face some financial trouble during this year since your expenditure will be way too high as compared to your earnings. You will be prone to injuries so be extra careful while going out. The year will be favourable for students as their energy and dynamism will help in facing competition. Your relationship with your elder siblings will improve and you may get some financial benefit or assistance from them. You will be quite optimistic throughout the year which will help you in overcoming any challenge.
    </string>
    <!--rasifal end-->

    <!--Personality Number-->
    <string name="one">
        Some of their key traits are:\n\n

Confidence.\n
Loyalty.\n
Leadership skills.\n
Creativity.\n
Ones need to work on:\n\n

Their ego.\n
Their lack of compassion.\n
Being overconfident.\n
Stubbornness.\n
Ones are born leaders. Is that surprising at all? Probably not because they have an ego, and they’re stubborn about it.\n

They’re risk-taking, self-driven pioneers who fear nothing and nobody. They’re also very creative, and a creative leader is a great one, right?\n

People might not be so sure about that. Ones are so full of confidence; they scare people off. They need to calm down, approach things with less vigor and keep their ego in check. Let people who lack the confidence get close to them, as people are afraid to as ones are now.\n\n

Work compassionately, lead gently and people will flock to ones.\n
    </string>
    <string name="two">
        Some of their key traits are:

Being trustworthy.
Honesty.
Reliability.
Friendly.
Twos need to work on:

Moodiness.
Shyness.
Personality number 2s are the best kind of friends. They’re trustworthy so you can confide in them, and they’re honest. If you tell them something they don’t like they’ll let you know, but in a warm way that keeps the peace.

Twos are natural peacemakers, but they’ll fight if they have to. They’re fiery despite their shy nature. Perhaps keeping the fight inside is what makes them so moody.

Despite the moodiness, twos are talented with great ideas and are very philosophical. You may admire them for these traits, and their soft natured warmth.
    </string>
    <string name="three">
        Some of their key traits are:

Opportunistic nature.
Intuition.
Communication skills.
Creativity.
Threes need to work on:

Manipulative streak.
Threes are talkative and talented at it. They can attract people easily with excellent communication skills, and keep them with their creativity.

It’s easy for threes to make friends, maybe because of their chatty side, maybe because of their lucky streak. Or maybe it’s because threes are intelligent and opportunistic, so they know when to pounce on a person. They’re fast at making wise decisions, which makes them successful in all aspects of life.

However, threes sometimes come across as being manipulative. Even if it’s unintentional, that’s something threes need to work on.
    </string>
    <string name="four">
        Some of their key traits are:

Family-oriented.
Well-dressed.
Stability.
Maturity.
Nurturing nature.
Pragmatic.
Fours need to work on:

Being too serious.
Dull attitude.
Fours make for the perfect gentlefolk. They’re organized, well dressed, and are very close to their family. They’re the types of well put together people that others turn to in a crisis.

Personality number 4s are very mature, even from a young age. They’re pragmatic in their outlook, consistent in their actions and they dominate any scenario. But they won’t put you down if you don’t match their stable, unshakeable ways. They’re very nurturing towards others and make for excellent managers, helpers and guides.

However, their pragmatic, systematic outlook in life makes them come across as boring. They’re too serious and need to learn to loosen up a little.
    </string>
    <string name="five">
        Some of their key traits are:

High spirited.
Travel enthusiast.
Adaptable.
Fives need to work on:

Over-burdening.
Fives are a joy to know. Their spirits are so high it’s breathtaking, and they love to travel. What else would a risk-taker who loves life do, right?

Personality number 5 people can handle almost any challenge, and they’ll fight zestily if anything goes awry. They’re very good at handling change and challenges, positive and negative. The positive changes they like are trends and pop culture, but the negatives could be anything.

Fives only falter when they work too hard when something goes wrong. They tend to overburden themselves, whether it’s at work or being everyone’s shoulder to cry on.
    </string>
    <string name="six">
        Some of their key traits are:

Warmth.
Well-balanced.
Responsible.
Caring.
Sixes need to work on:

Over-worrying.
Financial frivolity.
Vulnerability.
Sixes are generous beings who like caring for others. They’re friendly, so they’ll be warm and loving towards anyone right away. They’re so beautiful on the inside and care more about a person’s inside than outside.

However, sixes are very vulnerable when criticized and would do well to toughen up. They also tend to worry a lot, especially over money. They’re not particularly logical when it comes to their spending habits.
    </string>
    <string name="seven">
        Some of their key traits are:

Intelligence.
Rationality.
Dignified.
Sevens need to work on:

Reserved attitude.
Unemotional nature.
Sevens are intelligent, dignified people. Some might go as far as to call them scholars. No matter what the situation, they react with dignity and rationality.

Personality number 7 people make wonderful poets, aided by their intelligence and the air of mystery about them. Their work may be quirky, as are they, and they don’t care if you find it strange.

Although this confidence they have in themselves can sometimes be a downer. Sevens are used to people mocking their mysterious ways, their odd dress sense and their poetry. So they’ve adopted a reserved and “don’t-care” attitude about all aspects of life. Some people find this unappealing.
    </string>
    <string name="eight">
        Some of their key traits are:

Amazing judgment.
Successful.
Intuitive.
Controlled.
Eights need to work on:

Show-offiness.
Dominating people.
Eights are great judges of character. Their intuition is powerful, so they know the types of people they should be around. Because of this and their strong, self-controlled nature, they’re very successful in life.

However, their strong and controlled attitude may come across as too dominating to others, so they may shy away. They may also be disliked for showing off expensive things, like designer clothes. Eights can be very materialistic at times.

Though eights are persuasive when they want their way, they are not easily swayed by others.
    </string>
    <string name="nine">
        Some of their key traits are:

Influential.
Magnetic.
Charming.
Confidence.
Philanthropic.
Nines need to work on:

Being aloof.
Entitlement.
Nines are adored by many. They’re elegant, charismatic and graceful by nature. They have a raw magnetism that draws people in.

They keep people close with ease because they’re so well-versed, and their confidence is catching. But nines need to be careful because confidence can turn to cockiness in seconds.

Some nines even get aloof and start acting arrogant and self-entitled, with the more positive attention they get. It’s not ideal for an influential and charming person to come across in this manner.
    </string>
    <!--Personality Number End-->

    <!--alltext-->
    <string name="Expressionwhatistitle">
        What is Expression Number
    </string>
    <string name="ExpresionWhatisdes">
         The name is the first identity we all get. When we introduce ourselves, name is the first thing we tell other person. Name determines whether anyones life is peaceful, successful or not. It indicates that the type of people anybody attracts and the quality of person associate with them. It also indicates the nature of the experience they face, the kind of life they spend and opportunity and threats comes in their life.
  From the moment, parents gives the name to their child, the letters of his/her full name start working and impacting the childs life in the given sequence. Each letter is active for the number of years as per the value assigned to those letters. The letters of First Name, Middle Name, and Last name work simultaneously creating a unique pattern of events in an individuals life.
    </string>

    <string name="ExpresionHowtotitle">How to Calculate</string>
    <string name="ExpresionHowtodes"> Simply put, numerology is the study of the mystical relationship between our life and numbers. It is based on the numerical calculation of letters in names, with each letter having a corresponding number. These numbers can be used to evaluate your personality, life and even predict your future. The most popular numerology method in the western world is developed by Pythagoras, the famous Greek mathematician and philosopher, who believed that the universe is governed and explained by numbers. In the Pythagorean system, numbers were assigned to each letter in the alphabet. In name numerology, all numbers are reduced to the single digits 1. through 9 except the special master numbers 11 and 22. The numbers are reduced by simple addition.
</string>


    <string name="PersonalityWhatistitle">
           What is Personality Number
    </string>
    <string name="PersonalityWhatisdes">Personality number shows the way other people see you at first, the essence of your image. This number provides information on who you want to seem, the level of your confidence in communicating with others, how far can you go in your relationships and how open you are. Personality Number is one of the Core Numbers in Numerology. According to numerology, a personality number is a single-digit number that is derived from the consonants of your name.

 Personality number is a very important aspect that defines your characteristics, traits, qualities, and vibrations that you send in the world. It distinguishes what kind of people you will like, what facts you wil| accept and what things you will allow into your heart and mind. Personality number can reveal a lot of hidden traits about you.</string>
    <string name="PersonalityHowtotitle"> How to Calculate </string>
    <string name="PersonalityHowtodes">Personality number is developed by analyzing the consonants from your full name given to you at birth. In order to find this number add all the numbers assigned to the consonants from your full name (first name, last name, middle one if present), and reduce the result to the one-digit number.</string>


    <string name="SoulUrgeWhatistitle">What is Soul Urge Number </string>
    <string name="SoulUrgeWhatisdes">Soul Urge number is also known as Heart Desire Number. Soul
        number reveals your core desires and destiny. It define the general intention behind many of your actions, and dramatically influences the choices you make in life.The Soul Urge Number is also significant as it gives us more awareness about the reasons why we are drawn to specific things and why we do certain things. Soul Urge number gives you insight about your spiritual self (your soul). It tells you what you truly value, what your ethics are, what you desire at a deep, soul level, and how that inspires you along in this lifetime.</string>
    <string name="SoulUrgeHowtotitle">How to Calculate </string>
    <string name="SoulUrgeHowtodes">Soul urge number is derived from the vowels in your full name given to you at the birth. In order to find this number add all the numbers assigned to the vowels from your full name (first name, last name, middle one if present), and reduce the result to the one-digit number.</string>


    <string name="LifePathWhatistitle">What is Life Path Number
</string>
    <string name="LifePathWhatisdes">Numerology is the belief in the divine or mystical relationship between a number and events. The most important and influential number in your personal Numerology is your Life Path number. This number represents who you are at your core. It tell you what traits or skills you posses, and what major life challenges you may see along the way. Life Path number in Numerology is like the Sun sign in Astrology: It tells you like how you act and react, and how you process life. But do not think of it as a simple list of traits that are meant to tell you exactly who you are. While each Life Path carries a unique set of both positive and negative traits, how they manifest is up to you.
The life path number is a calculation that helps to predict the challenges in life, your current life status, future events and the purpose of your existence. The simple equation can show the life path number for anyone and exhibit your deepest values and personality as an individual.The life path numbers are only in single digits 1 to 9. Within these numbers all the prediction takes place. In the overall study of numerology, the life path number is most important. It will showcase the series of events, challenges, opportunities that you are about to spectate in your future life.</string>
    <string name="LifePathHowtotitle">How to Calculate </string>
    <string name="LifePathHowtodes">Life Path Number is calculated from your FULL Date of Birth, and is considered one of the most important and influential numbers within your entire Numerology Chart. In order to find your Life Path number, simply take your birthdate and reduce it down to its numerical value. For example, if you were born on July 5, 1989, youd first identify the separate values of the day, month, and year: July is the seventh month, so its number is seven. Your day of birth is, obviously, five. Finally, your birth year can be reduced down to a single number by adding its digits together (1+9+8+9 = 27) and then adding that sums digits together (2+7 = 9). So, you now have three numbers you need to add together (7+5+9 = 22) and yet another sum to reduce (2+2 = 4).</string>

    <string name="AttitudeWhatistitle">What is Attitude Number</string>
    <string name="AttitudeWhatisdes">The attitude number, also known as the sun and achievement number. Attitude Number describes how we are perceived by others when they first meet us. It is an indication of what type of first impression, or appearance, we portray to the world. The ways you act and react to the different circumstances in your personal, professional and social life characterizes your attitude towards life. Your way of thinking, your consideration for others attitudes, instincts and some basic personality traits also give a clear impression of your attitude.</string>
    <string name="AttitudeHowtotitle">How to Calculate </string>
    <string name="AttitudeHowtodes">In order to calculate attitude number need to add Birth Day and Birth Month together, and reducing that number down to a single digit number. Achievement/Attitude number reveals a lot about anyone innate abilities to have success in what they choose to do.</string>

    <string name="BirthWhatistitle">What is Birth Number </string>
    <string name="BirthWhatisdes">Birthday number is one of most important number in Numerology core numbers. This is derived from your birth date and the number that influence you most strongly throughout your life. As one of these important numbers, your Birthday number can reveal unique and powerful abilities that you naturally possess you have to offer the world. The day on which you were born is marked by certain properties.. It is the code of fate that will prepare you for a collision with the turns of fate that can cause damage to everything that seemed to be the guarantors of a successful future. The number of your birthday can be either one or two digits. Each figure has its own characteristics. </string>
    <string name="BirthHowtotitle">How to Calculate </string>
    <string name="BirthHowtodes">According to Numerology, your birth number says a lot about your personality and characteristics.Add the numbers in your date of birth, the result you get is your Birth Number. For example, if the date of birth of an individual is 2nd March 1989, the birth number would be 2, because the person is born on 2nd of March, i.e. 2nd day in the month of March. If a persons birth date is in two digits, i.e. 17th, then their birth number will be 1+7=8.</string>


    <!--Halth and Work-->
    <!--title-->
    <string name="behaviourtitle">Behaviour Reading</string>
    <string name="careertitle">Career Readeing</string>
    <string name="healthtitle">Health Reading</string>
    <string name="moneytitle">Money Reading</string>

</resources>